<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HandiMaps InternshipProject</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>

    <!--Main Activity-->
    <string name="Introduction">
        Hello HandiMaps, my name is Payson Blackwell and I am a Software Developer who is interested to learn and be helpful to the team!
    </string>


    <!--Tabbed Activity-->
    <string name="title_activity_about">AboutActivity</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Early Life</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">School</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Interests</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>

    <string name="section_text_1">
        \t    I grew up in Northern California, in a town near Sacramento, until the age of 10. It was a small town where a lot of people knew each other and I still have family there that I visit.\n\n

        \t    When I moved to Kirkland, it took some time getting used to the weather of the Pacific Northwest, but now I have come to enjoy the rain.
                About 10 years later, I am now 21 years old, and really appreciating all the different possibilities that are around this area.
    </string>
    <string name="section_text_2">
        \t    A major part of my MiddleSchool and part of my HighSchool, was playing in band. It was always felt like a treat during my day to play my Trombone and work together as a band to create great sounding music.
                That was the first time I realized how fun it was to take a set of tools and create something I am proud of with it.\n\n

        \t    During my Junior year of High School, I decided to take advantage of a school program called Running Start, which allowed me to take college classes at the same time as my regular classes.
                I had never done any sort of coding before, but heard that it was mostly problem solving. I decided to try it out and instantly took a liking to it.
                After a year in the program, I started a part time job being a Peer Tutor and helping software development students to debug their homework, go over concepts, and more.\n\n

        \t    I am currently still taking classes at LWTech and am a part of the first cohort of the school\'s Bachelor\'s Degree for Software Development. It has been very helpful and taught me more than I thought it would.
    </string>
    <string name="section_text_3">
        \t    There are many things that I like to do in my free time, Here is a list of some of them. \n\n
                \u2022 Reading\n
                \u2022 Playing Video Games \u0026 Board Games\n
                \u2022 Walking my Dog\n
                \u2022 Taking Tutorials/Learning\n
                \u2022 Listening to AudioBooks \u0026 Podcasts\n
    </string>

    <!--Coding Activity-->
    <string name="coding_text">
        \t    I have now been coding for about 5 years and have messed with a bunch of different stuff. I have worked in C++, Java, C#, Python, and I\'ve dabbled in a few others.
                I think I enjoy writing in Java and C# the most, and really enjoy working on projects where I can see my work being used. \n\n

        \t    My first major project was a C# game in Unity, in which I was the only developer on a 3 person team. I took the sprite artwork of the other two people and was able to follow tutorials online
                to teach myself how to use Unity. It was first time to easily show others what I could do and it was really satisfying to learn and see it take shape.

        \t    Since I have been in school for my entire Software Development Career so far, I don\'t have any major projects that I have done in my spare time.
                My next personal project is to learn more about machine learning and create something simple but useful with it.
    </string>

    <!--Future Activity-->
    <string name="future_text">
        A lot of time during interviews, the employer asks questions about the applicant\'s career and future, Here is a quick overview of my answers\n\n
        
        <b>Why do you want to work here?</b>\n
        I am interested to try out new things, get better at developing apps and working in a team. I am also excited to be able to help others with the goal of HandiMaps.
        \n\n

        <b>Where do you see yourself in 5 years?</b>\n
        I am honestly not quite sure. There are a lot of different opportunities around this area and I haven\'t tried out all the different pathways that programming allows.
        \n\n

        <b>What is your dream job?</b>\n
        It would have to be one where I feel useful and constantly learn new things during my workday. I do have a soft spot for trying out game development,
                so I might try that out one day and see how it would feel as my full time job.
        \n\n
        <b>What is your biggest weakness?</b>\n
        I am not usually a fan of this question, but it is a useful one. For me, it is probably my lack of experience in a proper software development job. At least the part time tutoring I do help me to stay sharp on most subjects in programming
    </string>

    <!--Maps Activity-->
    <string name="explain_text">
        As part of me taking the time to make this app, I deceived to learn something new. Here is the result of me trying out a fragment for this first time, and working with the Google Maps Api
    </string>

</resources>
